fruitsandveggiesmorematters.org 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Have A Plant

Our overall policy is to use our best efforts to respect the privacy of all of our on-line guests. Our web server recognizes and records certain non-personal information about visitors; specifically, this information consists only of the type of browser used and the domain name of the visitor’s Internet service provider. This information is used only for internal review purposes such as tracking the total number of visitors to our site on an aggregate, non-personally identifiable information basis. We do not access any personally identifiable facts in this process. Non-personally identifiable information is information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information (like age, profession or gender). We do not require you to register or provide information in order to view our sites.

We do not collect personal information from visitors to our site unless it is provided to us voluntarily and knowingly. Produce for Better Health Foundation does not give or sell to anyone any information we may collect at our site.

Cookies Policy

Last updated: March 23, 2018

Produce for Better Health Foundation (PBH) uses cookies on FruitsAndVeggies.org (the “Service”). By using the Service, you consent to the use of cookies.

Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third-parties we may partner with may use cookies on the Service, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.

What are cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you.

Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies.

How PBH uses cookies

When you use and access the Service, we may place a number of cookies files in your web browser.

We may use cookies for the following purposes: to enable certain functions of the Service, to provide analytics, to store your preferences, to enable advertisements delivery, including behavioral advertising.

We may use both session and persistent cookies on the Service and we use different types of cookies to run the Service:

– Essential cookies. We may use essential cookies to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts.

Third-party cookies

In addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Service, deliver advertisements on and through the Service, and so on.

What are your choices regarding cookies

If you’d like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.
